# **ALINA HUZ**

## UI/UX Designer

© Ennis, Clare, Ireland

**6** +353 85 202 27 36

☑ alina.huz.design@gmail.com

Bē @alinahuz

I am a UI/UX designer whose motivation is to exceed expectations, with over 2 years of experience within the industry. During this time, I gained experience in developing designs for websites in various fields of activity. I approach each project individually. I am set for professional growth with each project, open to gaining new knowledge and mastering new technologies.

Domains in which I worked: Logistics and transport (B2B, B2C), Healthcare, Insurance, E-commerce

In the future, I see for myself a vector of development in user experience research because I want to be involved in creating products that win the hearts of users. Who knows? Maybe soon I will be part of a team that will create a strong competitor for Instagram, Facebook, Snapchat, or TikTok.

I'm considering remote work or office. Open for relocation inside Ireland.

#### EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer 🛱 1 year 2 months

Freelance / February 2021 - April 2022

#### Main responsibilities:

- · Communication with clients, briefing, analysis of the received data, implementation of personas, user flow cards, prediction of interaction scenarios, analysis of the target audience and competitors, determination of the goals and objectives of the project;
- · Creation of moodboards and concepts, prototyping and quick sketching;
- · Development of design of landings, banners, multi-page sites, logos;
- · Presentation of your work, preparation of files for layout, collaboration with Frontend developer.

UI/UX Designer **□** 8 months

"Delivery group" (Kyiv, Ukraine) Contract / July 2020 - February 2021

#### Main responsibilities:

- · Communication with clients, briefing, analysis of the received data, analysis of the target audience and competitors, determination of the goals and objectives of the project, development of site architecture, interaction scenarios;
- · Collection of information among employees of the main office of the company, who were also part of the target audience:
- · Development and testing of a prototype;
- · Development of design of multi-page sites, banners, redesign;
- · Presentation of your work directly to the product owner, preparation of files for layout, collaboration with Frontend developer and digital manager.

UI/UX Designer 5 months

Freelance / March 2020 - July 2020

# Main responsibilities:

- · Communication with clients, briefing, analysis of the received data, analysis of the target audience and competitors, determination of the goals and objectives of the project;
- · Development of design for landing pages, banners, multi-page sites, redesign;
- · Presentation of your work, preparation of files for layout, collaboration with Frontend developer.

# SKILLS

- · Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD
- Low/high fidelity Wireframing
- · Banners / Animation banners
- · Typographic logo design
- · Responsive and adaptable design
- · Rapid Prototyping
- Moodboards
- · UI-kits in Figma: components, auto layouts, styles, variations
- · Knowledge of wireframe tools Lucid/ Mural/ Wireframe.cc
- Strong knowledge of UI/UX principles
- · I can do research, realisation of personas, user flow maps, prediction of interaction scenarios
- · Understanding the principles of Atomic Design
- · Application of User-centric design methodology
- Understanding the principles of Agile/SCRUM
- · Teamwork with developers, tester, product manager

Public institution Beryslav Medical College Kherson Regional Council

Secondary vocational, Pharmacy/sept. 2013 - June 2016

Zaporizhzhia State Medical University Bachelor, Pharmacy/sept. 2016 - Jun 2018

**EDUCATION** 

## LANGUAGE

**English** - B2 (In progres) Ukrainian - Native

## CERTIFICATES

"Web designer course" 2019

Educational platform "WayUp" (3 months)

"UX Crash Course: Fundamentals" 2019

Information resource "Medium" (1 month)

"UX from scratch: how to become a UI designer" 2022 Course from Udemy (2 weeks)

"Design Basics" 2022

Course from Mate Academy (2 weeks)

"Digital Skills: User Experience" 2022

Course from FutureLearn (3 weeks)